Hey! Hey! Hey!
Quiet!
Put this on.
Hey. why are you taking him out?
He's one of theirs.
A Nip traitor.
Hey. we're talking to you.
We're gonna die if you keep us in shit like this.
Get in there.
It'll be soon!
Kneel down!
How did you survive this long. Second Lieutenant?
Is this due to the guidance of the God you believe in?
You don't deserve to bear this!
Your sin deserves only one thing:
the death penalty!
But the higher-ups say.
You should be executed in our country.
You will be made an example of.
in front of thousands of people.
But
on my ship
I can decide how I deal with you.
He is one of the prisoners who tried to escape last night.
It would be too easy to simply kill him.
We will keep this beast... alive and also make an example of it.
You both will
soon realize
who your true enemy is.
God has abandoned you.
We're under fire! Multiple targets!
To the anti-aircraft guns!
Send reinforcements!
Aaah!
Come on!
Torpedo!
Piece of shit.
What was that thing?
Did you see it?
Did you see what did this?
What does this. a...
Dear God. please forgive me.
Are you fucking crazy?
Hey.
Look at me.
If this thing comes back.
we need to be ready for it.
You... You take this.
I keep this.
One doesn't work without the other.
You understand?
Look. Food.
This could come in handy.
Smokes.
You smoke?
All right. More for me. then.
Look. Coffee.
You drink coffee. right?
I knew this boy.
He was young.
Innocent.
Tortured for no reason.
You bastards!
Why did you do this to us?
You're animals!
All of you! Inhuman!
Sleep well. mate.
God.
Wear these.
They're just as good.
No. not for me. mate.
They'll look better on you.
Here. eat something.
Fuck's sake!
Shit.
Take this.
No. no. It's fine. I'll have this.
Take it.
I'll leave it there.
This is the best damn meal I have had in a long time.
Almost reminds me of home.
Bronson.
My name. Bronson.
Blonson.
Yeah.
Bronson.
Yeah. Near enough.
You?
Saito.
Why are you chained up with me?
Doesn't make us too different. is all.
Yes! Finished.
Get this chain.
Okay.
Wait!
Hit there.
Look at it closely.
There.
Are you sure?
It's a bit close. mate.
It's okay.
Aim there.
Okay.
That's okay.
Right there.
Yes!
Yes.
Now it's my turn.
Don't worry.
Wait. wait. wait. wait.
Are you sure about this?
Okay. Go on. then.
Then let's go.
Now you're free.
Yes! Yes!
Me and you. we make a good team.
And we can work together on this island.
The bullet. Give me the bullet.
Look at this.
That's the sea creature again.
Move!
Come on.
Run faster!
Come on. faster!
Hide.
Here. take this.
Trust me.
Wait. stop.
I smell something.
Look.
Don't shoot!
He's one of us. Are you okay?
How long have you been here?
Since this morning.
Cigarettes!
-Are you from that ship? -Yes.
We survived because we were wearing life jackets.
Everyone else drowned.
Poor bastards.
Hey! Give it to me.
Some water?
Is no one else here?
Just you?
Yes.
Before we were attacked.
there was a rumor
that a traitor and a fugitive had been chained together.
That sort of thing spreads quickly on a ship.
Everyone bet on
who would kill whom first.
On who would kill who first.
Hey. Where is he?
He's dead.
Drowned.
Ah yes. And you swam to the island with the body?
You... are not only a traitor.
but also a liar.
Where is he?
Orang Ikan.
Hey.
Go.
Jesus Christ!
Bronson. get out of here.
Wait.
Saito.
Hold on.
Saito. wait.
Wait!
Saito. Saito!
What the fuck are you?
Get out of here!
Bronson.
Fuck.
Saito.
Bronson.
You're shaking. Here. This will warm you.
No. Let's go.
That one.
Cigarette?
What's in there?
This way.
It's a mermaid.
A mother.
Bronson. it's dangerous here. Come on!
We cannot let this creature live.
Wait.
If we kill her child. she'll only become more vengeful.
No. look. It's either us or them.
It's either us or them.
I've got an idea.
Come on. with me.
Come on.
In there. Come on.
Come on. Look!
Bomb. In there.
Boom.
That's it. That's it.
Okay. Just here.
That's it. Just here.
Okay. It's a delayed-action fuse.
Christ. It's bent.
Need a tool or something.
No. wait.
Bronson.
It's no good. It won't work.
No. no. no.
Wait. the crash axe.
Yeah. it's in the cockpit. We could use that.
Yeah. one good hit with that.
and then four. three. two. one. boom!
Bronson.
One of us is gonna have to stay here with the bomb.
Me or you here.
One of us here.
My life
has led me right here.
We need that axe.
We go together. You cover me.
Go!
Let's do this.
Here. Take this.
Come on. then. bitch.
Okay. Cover me.
Ready. Bronson?
It's working. it's working.
It's working.
I've got it.
Bronson!
Bronson. are you okay?
I'm fucking finished.
Take this.
Take it.
Go.
Get out of here. Saito.
Bronson.
Go. Saito. Go.
Run. Saito. run!
Come closer. bitch.
Four. three. two...
Fuck.
It's okay.
Focus.
Aim there...
See you in hell. bitch.
Come on!
Who was Bronson?
Was he a prisoner?
US DEPARTMENT OF THE NAVAL SERVICE
Did he help you?
Were you a prisoner?
Were you on this ship?
On the ship with the prisoners.
Ask him how he got himself in the brig.
What did you do?
I killed my superior officer.
I couldn't let my comrades die senselessly.
So I killed the man who gave the order.
He killed his commanding officer.
Ask him about this guy Bronson.
Bronson.
Yeah.
Cigarettes.
You smoke?
Trust me.
Me and you. we make a good team.
Come on. then. bitch!
We can work together on this island.
Doesn't make us too different.
Bronson!
He was
my friend.
They were friends.
Is anyone else on the island?
No. there's no one there anymore.
Sailors. we're shipping off home now.
Full speed ahead.